what's up everyone today we're gonna be
doing Venus in the sixth house let's not
waste time because it's a beautiful day
and you know what I like doing a
beautiful full day
oh that's coffee again so the sixth
house what is the sixth house sixth
house represents your competitive
enemies and your real enemies enemies
are gonna come and do the drive-by on
your house okay six hours all mainly
don't represent in a civilized world
your enemies at your work your
competitor your competitor pretty much
people who are at your office fighting
for those sales figures so they can
either get a promotion and keep their
job mainly that's what it means nowadays
like winning the competition you keep
your job okay
sixth house represents litigations and
proceeding of divorce
meaning that process of great get going
through a divorce is represent about six
hours or presents everyday work life it
represents diseases or miss Menken main
function is for the diseases that things
that oppose you pretty much that's what
six thousand six thousand --tz-- small
animals wild animals or not small
obtained animals or wild animals you
know could be your cat dogs rats I don't
know who's gonna keep rat as their pet
lizard
don't ask me okay
it represents all sorts of things you
know so love for animals if they're kind
of like that crocodiles Crocodile Dundee
you know like oh look over here there's
a prick coolkid I'm I'm gonna go touch
him right now let's go see it bad guy
you know like when you seen National
Geographic those people who are looking
at the animals studying them wanting to
be with them that's what you know this
represents so what is Venus Venus is
that compassion Venus is love
relationships passion in life Venus
represents convenience e happiness
things that make you happy so what
crocodile then these are these people do
in that National Geographic Channel
represents this combination of Venus in
the sixth house okay so when I see Venus
in the sixth house the first thing I see
is a social worker person who's there to
for the benefit of the others person
who's there to help the unprivileged
people who can't help themselves like
animals okay because animal need
constant care you can just leave a dog
in the house and expect him to find his
own food in his own water you have to
provide it to them
that's what Venus is and Social Work can
represent anything working with homeless
people working with orphaned children
working with people who like in FEMA
like if the disaster happens you know
they're there to help them okay it also
represents working with agreements
working with contracts so a lawyer
looked President Obama sixth house
person you know working with with
conflicts with agreements and contracts
okay so that's what this really
signifies a in the sixth house you know
like someone like Princess Diana who was
there you know these are this is what it
really represents so when you have Venus
in the sixth house you know it strongly
can indicate somebody who's a
veterinarian first of all who's has love
for the animals you know you can be
anything in the veterinarian world you
can be a wet anarion technician you can
be a groomer you can be you know an
actual doctor for the animals I can also
represent medicines world for the
unprivileged also but mainly you know in
animal world is seeing this people who
open up orphaned clinic not clinic
meaning like orphan housing are seen
from this like Anil Kapoor and mr. India
okay like that but here Venus can also
signify divorce because Venus is a
significant of marriage okay and when it
comes to the sixth house meaning it's
gone it's in the house of what it rip
opposite of what it represents so when
this represents love in the relationship
six house represents the breaking of
that so it can signifies that unless
Venus is a yoga Kaka for your ascendant
yoga kharka me
that Venus is ruling the quadrant and
the trend houses meaning the first forty
seventh and tenth house and at the same
time it's ruling the fifth and ninth
house so it becomes strong okay when
that happens then it's the Venus energy
will do whatever it can to protect the
significance of those houses okay but if
Venus is being aspected by the sixth
lord while it's in the sixth house or in
conjunction for the sixth floor then it
can really signify a divorce but here
what happens is since this is not a very
well place for Venus most of the time
these people will run into a lot of
conflict in making deals making
agreements trying to get a deal done it
will be they'll have a lot of
opposition's and that so if you want to
have a contract sign let's say you're a
lawyer and you want to get a contract
signed from your opposing party you want
to agree on it you came to an agreement
last minute they can just change their
mind I know I want this deal this deal
they said otherwise I'm not gonna sign
it and you know you can't do that so it
keeps you in that conflict state of all
things okay here these people are very
pleasant to their servants so you know
why in India even nowadays it's so
sickening that how people treat their
servants I and some of the other Indian
grocery store when the owner is there
the way he treats his normal workers
were cashiers and you know who are just
working there it's like he thinks it's
India you know and that's what it's what
opposite of Venus in the sixth houses
they want they there have tremendous
respect for people who take care of them
so if this these people have a cleaner
lady in the house cleaning things they
will do they will offer her food devil
off for her drinks they you know like in
India they will sit down on the on the
floor instead of the chair no these
people will say you know sit down on a
chair I mean I cannot ever imagine even
being in India and having my servant
talk to me while they're sitting down
and I'm sitting on a chair I mean this
is just disgraceful oh yeah I hope you
don't do that or everybody is watching
in India because
you you are really just just going to
the lowest point of a soul
your servant should sit on the dining
table with you
your servant should sit on a sofa with
you you should be able to do that no
matter where your venus is placed okay
that's that's just human dignity that's
that's you know prevailing your soul to
the highest level if you do that so
that's what basically you know these
energy represents here so like I said
you know the easiest way define your
career besides going through all those
technical things that I've showed you in
in previous videos like looking at your
up mccockiner Master caca the two things
you can look for is your moon and Venus
moon represents your mind where your
mind is all the time okay and your Venus
where what's your passion what is it
that makes you happy so if you have
Venus in the sixth house you'll be
absolutely happy in the things that I
just told you
working in a social working environment
social workers working with animals
working with unprivileged people if you
are still if you're in your early 20s
you may not realize it okay this is why
I think the horse whenever a
consultation happened I don't think
anybody should do a consultation on till
they're 30 because your mind is still
developing man even at 25 you're still
not there
not until you hit your 32 and above
that's when you really know who you are
so at 25 you may not love animals at 32
you may love animals a lot of time it
happens okay
so just look at these two positions of
mind and happiness and you'll know what
to do okay so guys this was my analysis
on Venus in the sixth house hope you
enjoyed it if you new to my channel
subscribe above and if you want to know
more about astrology and very Venus's
place and where other planets are placed
so you can look at your own self and
come back to my channel on studying more
stuff check out my link below check out
my book there strategy the speed of
light and when you get the book follow
the directions I'll send you the link to
study your own charts your own
divisional charts and everything so just
follow the directions of the link below
otherwise I am gonna see you tomorrow
otherwise bye bye oh look over there a
dinosaur I'm gonna ride on him
[Music]